I had a video absolutely bomb,
and the feedback from it has been
beyond negative. However,
there's some lessons
that you can learn from this, and
I'm going to go through them now.
I had a bit of fun last week
and I decided to
wrap my new car. And I thought,
do you know what?
Let's film some of it and show people,
because it could be aspirational.
I don't know about you,
every young man out there probably wishes
one day to have a
sports car. And then out of them,
some of them probably would like to
customize it
in some way or wrap it,
watch a bit of Matt Armstrong.
I don't know.
So here it is, the 10 out of 10. Now,
I haven't got a problem with the video
being
a 10 out of 10,
and to lose 55 subscribers, fine.
But it's the comments. "You
are everything you complained about
and more." "Looks
dog shit." And there was one right,
that said, "James used to be so
relatable back when you were struggling.
Now I don't like who you've become." Hold
on, mate. Just let me clear this up.
You were happier when I was struggling.
Cool. Got that. Nice one.
One of the best bits of advice I've given
people is, if you're trying to grow your
email list,
don't offer people a free mug to join
because you'll only
attract people that want a free mug.
But to put this into perspective,
main channel since launch, 46
million views,
97,000 pounds in the pocket.
Let's do the maths.
These are my YouTube stats.
How much did I get paid
per view? £2.12 per thousand views.
The next day when I woke up, I thought,
"I should have posted this on the small
channel," because they're the people
that are hungry, aspirational,
and don't just
hate anyone doing well, I hope.
Now on this channel, I don't even have
monetization turned on because I don't
care. But let's work this out.
Lifetime, 1.4 million views. What about
1.4 million views and then all time.
That's good.
About tick $2.5 million. We'll take that.
Your rate is over 800 times higher than
the previous.
The small channel,
800 times more because I didn't
attract the wrong audience.
Now before you get excited
that you can make
$2.4 million, was it March, in 14 months?
Let's actually break this down. When
was the first sale I made?
USD, so it's December.
How many dollars per day is that?
$5,100 US per day since we launched.
Now some of you might be thinking, "Oh,
but Alex Hormozi makes more than that."
Probably way more. In fact,
if you find any YouTube entrepreneur,
they make way
more than me.
But just before I tell you the lessons
that I promised earlier, what
I think is the kind of unique selling
point here is, one,
when you join my program,
it's actually me. I don't have any staff.
It's me in the Discord all day.
James, James,
James, James, James, James, James, James,
James, James. It's just me.
It's probably the biggest downfall of the
whole program, if I'm honest.
But if an entrepreneur
is making 500 million a year, how
are you supposed to
aspire or connect with that at all?
Ten years ago, I became a PT.
2020, wrote my first book.
Only became the villain arc business guru
a year
ago. Got a mediocre education,
got really bad ADHD, and I never
had any friends that did this growing up.
Not to mention,
I didn't study in any business mentorships
that told me exactly how
to do it or gave me the blueprint.
So I'd like to think that my story
is quite
aspirational because you can actually
accomplish it.
If you want to get Alex Hormozi's level of
success, unlikely.
I'm not even going to get that.
$5,000 US a day, never done a sales call.
I'll even show you. So we launched,
I'll be honest with you as well,
I had to put
the price up of the mentorship to $2,500.
I thought some people
are going to see that
and think that's expensive.
So I started doing a one-to-one
application only program where you pay me
grand, we do 10 calls over 10 weeks,
or we can space it out a little bit
longer.
Pretty much,
we work one-to-one for 10 weeks.
I only put it there,
so it made this look cheaper.
I've had so many applications for this in
the first week, I've had to put the price
up.
I've now signed four people onto this in
the last seven days.
None of them needed a sales call.
I just said to them, "If I don't make you
significantly more than 10 grand back,
I'll give you your money back." One other
guy said, "James,
I have a big accountancy business.
How can you help me?" I did a little
screen recording and just said,
"This needs to
change. This needs to change.
You're probably better off talking about
this." Sent
him a three-minute video. Boom,
paid straight away.
So the whole idea
that you need to be doing sales calls,
nah.
The majority of people
that we get into this,
simple email sign up.
So this is what I've been promoting on
YouTube, "30 Ways in 30 Days to Optimize
Your Business." There's a link to this in
the description.
This gets the majority of people into it.
Basically, again, for you
and your business, if you just create 20,
30, 40 amazing little tips,
put them into an email autoresponder.
Just ask yourself,
"If I sent this to someone every single
day, would they buy
my shit?" And evidently, if you do
that well, you do.
And all of my social media actually
funnels towards that.
Now, the other thing to talk about
is these prices keep going up,
and it's not
because I'm greedy, it's purely demand.
Because I'm in here every single day,
I know exactly how busy this is,
and if any days I feel a little bit
overwhelmed or a little bit like there's
too
much going on, I just put the prices up.
It has not slowed down sales at all since
we began.
I started this at $800 US,
so we're now at 2,500 in 14 months,
which is
great. Same goes for your business.
If you want to be more expensive,
just build more demand.
And the beautiful thing here is
that this channel has got only 28,000
subscribers. Within a year,
this could be at 50, 60, 100,000
subscribers, which
is only going to mean more demand.
More demand is going to mean more people
wanting to be in the mentorship, which is
going to mean prices
are only going to go up.
And the content that I use to grow the
channel is going to be based off the stuff
that I learn in the Discord. Which
is again, my final point.
It is so much better you lot being busy
than it is you being expensive.
Because although at the moment,
I won't lie to you,
I have no work-life balance.
I spend all day, every day in here.
It's now 10:00 a.m. in the morning.
I was up at 4:00 because of jet lag,
and I've just been working in
here all day. But the beauty of this is,
I have my finger on the
pulse of every single problem businesses
are facing right now through social
media, Instagram, everything,
because I'm all day,
every day helping these people.
Like Doc,
you probably see his video this week,
60,000 followers from one
reel. Mad.
But I cannot believe I thought it
was a good idea to post the car wrap
on the big channel
and expect them to be happy with it.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I cannot say this any clearer.
Please optimize your content for clients,
not for big
followings,
because so many of my subscribers on
that big
channel are the type of people
that follow Gary economics.
"Tax the rich. If you've got money,
it's making other people poor." I can't
help
but feel that all these viral videos
that I did about Logan Paul,
Steven Bartlett,
Piers Morgan,
they've just brought me in people
that never wanted to see me
succeed.
They just wanted to have viral videos put
in front of them. Look at that.
I'm 35 and I'm still learning.
Never making that mistake again.
Any other posts about the Porsche
are all going on this channel because I
hope
it'll be you in a couple of years' time.
And when we see people doing well,
we should be happy for them because it
should
show us that there
is a path to achieve the exact same
things, not to hate on them
to make us feel better for our own levels
of inaction. Bonkers.
Just wanted to get that out of my system.
Links are in the description as per usual.
See you guys next week.